keep it going for the reason Mike Pence
says we have hurricanes
you look like the little man on top of a
wedding cake that a bakery would refuse
to make for you
Will and Grace was really the best you
could do it just
just jack just jack is uh it's also what
I'm gonna do in my hotel room alone
after sitting next to Blake Griffin all
night Jesus Christ you're so I'd
you in front of my grandparents I that's
how
I almost want to you know I feel like
Mimi would be proud
like you look like a black guy that got
made by a printer running out of ink
that's
yeah
Chris Redd is here because Comedy
Central wasn't sure if Blake was black
or not
you look great Chris you were stressed
like a nine-year-old who just found a
thousand dollars on the sidewalk
at this point like what can we say about
Jeff Ross that he hasn't heard before
it's like oh I respect you
you look nice tonight here's your salad
sir stuff like that okay Jeff you look
like if pop I only ate Popeyes check
that
no Jeff no don't break the couch your
face your face has a dad bod let's Jeff
gets really hot girls and I just I don't
how do you get tens teens I'm sorry I
read that wrong how did you get you have
the sex appeal of a gymnastics doctor I
just don't understand
robert de niro is here
looking like Alf
[Applause]
I can't even believe I I get to share
this stage with you tonight Roberts
narrow and by this stage I mean the
final one of your life it's
I'm sorry we don't feel right about any
of this
Caitlyn Jenner I just want to thank you
for all you've done for the trans
movement in the size 16 stiletto
industry you are such an incredible
athlete people forget just how fast you
once ran from your first family to go be
on a reality show
[Applause]
seriously though I know being a new mom
is hard but even Casey Anthony knows the
current location of her daughter
[Applause]
okay you're a Republican I don't know
why you've already gained control over a
woman's body
what does that party have to do to lose
your support of be your son
kaitlin I know you've only publicly
identified as a woman for a few years
but I just want you to know that I know
that deep down you have always been a
and I spelled with a k though for you
you're great thank you you're great Alec
Baldwin what an honor to be here
roasting Justin Bieber's wife's oldest
fattest uncle it's right I'll never
forget that voicemail that when you
called your daughter Ireland a a
thoughtless little pig I tell you one of
the worst things you can call your
daughter after Ireland actually that's
that name
yikes speaking of terrible names your
wife's name is hilarious is it hilarya
hello it's hilarious
Laura Neal our Hilaria I was so stupid
okay it doesn't matter she's so hot dude
she's so hot and fit does getting
screamed at burn calories
you have four kids under the age of six
I just how do you do it I mean isn't
your semen just oatmeal at this point Oh
Robert just got excited when I said
oatmeal he's sort of salivating your
night nurse is warming it up backstage
it'll be ready in the break I'm such a
fan of the Baldwin's I've never been so
sure that four people have buried a
hooker together in all seriousness I
want to thank Alec in his memoir he
bravely admitted that he had once
considered suicide and I just want to
say that that meant a lot to me because
I have also considered your suicide and
I have some ideas
I even know what I'm gonna wear
Alex thank you so much for having me
here tonight
comedy's
[Music]